Sylvia Beach Papers, 1887-1966 (bulk 1920s-1950s ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 7: Photographs, 1881-1969; 14.1 linear feet 20 boxes
  - Subseries 7F: Photographs of Notable People, 1881-1968 June 11; 10.0 boxes (1 partial)
    - Huebsch, Ben W., undated; 1.0 folder
      - Snapshot: Ben W. Huebsch Walking in Athanaeum Court, undated; 2; 1 photograph and 1 photograph of the print in a frame portion of 1 folder (0.6 x 0.3 inches, mounted on card 4.75 x 3.25 inches) (Folder 8)
        Inscribed on reverse "Athanaeum Court, 116 Piccadilly, London W1— Dear Sylvia Beach, You flattered me by asking for my portrait, so here it is by the grace of a street camera artist. It’s pretty awful, but I’m afraid that it is a good resemblance! It was good to see you again, and I shall hope for another visit next year.—Sincerely, B.W. Huebsch" A second very small image is of this photograph framed and on a floor, cut from a larger photograph.
      - Portrait: Ben W. Huebsch as a Young Man, undated; 1; 2 copies (5 x 4 inches) (Folder 8)
      - Infant Portrait: Eric Or Erik Huebsch, undated; 1; portion of 1 folder (2.25 x 3 inches) (Folder 8)
        "Eric Huebsch" written on recto, "Erik Huebsch at 14 months" written on reverse.
    - Hughes, Langston, 1937; portions of 2 boxes
      - Portrait: Langston Hughes in Front of Collage of Newsprint by Carl Van Vechten, circa 1937; 15; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964.; 1.0 folder (5.5 x 3.5 inches (mounted in frame 14.5 x 11.5)) (Folder 17)
        Inscribed "To Sylvia Beach, Sincerely, Langston Hughes, Paris, July 37," blind stamped "Photograph by Carl Van Vechten"
      - Copy Print: Langston Hughes in Front of Collage of Newsprint by Carl Van Vechten, circa 1937; 1; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964.; 1 folder (9.5 x 5.75 inches (mounted on card 10.5 x 6.75)) (Folder 9)
    - Jacob, Max, 1922 May 28; 1; 1.0 folder (6 x 4.75 inches) (Folder 10)
      One photograph of an inscribed sketch of Max Jacob. Inscription in sketch reads "à mon cher Michel, Max Jacob, 28 Mars 1922, fait chez notre ami Lasea[?]"
    - James, Henry, undated; 1.0 folder
      - Formal Portrait: Henry James With Beard From Éditions Robert Laffont, undated; 1; portion of 1 folder (9.25 x 7 inches) (Folder 11)
        Stamped on reverse "Éditions, Robert Laffont, 30, Rue de l’Université, Paris-VII"
      - Clipping: Formal Portrait of Henry James in Profile, undated; 2; portion of 1 folder (6.25 x 5 inches) (Folder 11)
      - Photographic Postcard of a reproduction: Painted Portrait of Henry James by John S. Sargent From the National Portrait Gallery, undated; 3; portion of 1 folder (5.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 11)
        Short biography by H.G. Wells on reverse with note: "Printed for the National Portrait Gallery, London, by B. Matthews (Photo Printers) Ltd., Bradford, England."
      - Clipping: Formal Portrait of Henry James in Profile, undated; 4; portion of 1 folder (4.25 x 3 inches) (Folder 11)
        Stamped on reverse "Shakespeare and Company, Bookshop, 12, Rue de l’Odéon, Paris VI"
    - John, Augustus, 1926 June 26; 1; 1.0 folder (13 x 9 inches) (Folder 12)
      Clipping of sketched portrait, titled "Augustus John," from "Supplement to The New Statesman, June 26, 1926"
    - Jones, Henry Festing, 1923 October-1924 May; 1.0 folder
      - Printed Postcard: Henry Festing Jones Holding an Infant, 1923 October 30; 1; portion of 1 folder (5.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 13)
        On reverse to "Miss Sylvia Beach (Shakespeare and Co), Rue de l’Odéon, Paris (France)": "120 Maida Vale W.9., 30 Oct. 1923, I am sending you as promised the least respectable photo of me that I can find. On the card it is me with my nephew’s daughter here in this house 15 years ago. Please give my kind regards to La Maison des Amis des Livres, that I am to yourself [from?] yours very sincerely, H. F. Jones"
      - Formal portrait: Henry Festing Jones, undated; 2; portion of 1 folder (5.75 x 4 inches, mounted on card 7.25 x 4.5 inches) (Folder 13)
      - Inscribed photogravure: Painted Portrait of Henry Festing Jones by George Clausen (1923), 1924 May; 3; portion of 1 folder (4.25 x 3.5 inches, mounted on board 10.25 x 8 inches) (Folder 13)
        Inscribed "May 1924, To Sylvia Beach from her devoted Henry Festing Jones"
      - Formal portrait: Henry Festing Jones by Maull & Fox, 1923 October; 4; Maull & Fox.; portion of 1 folder (6 x 4 inches, mounted on card 10.75 x 8 inches) (Folder 13)
        Inscribed "To Sylvia Beach with all manner of good wishes from Henry Festing Jones, October 1923"
    - Joyce, James, 1915-1939; portions of 5 boxes
      - Joyce, James: On Bloomsday by Sylvia Beach, 1925 June 16; 1.0 folder
        Note on envelope that housed images reads: "Photos of JJ taken by SB / Joyce on Blooms Day June 16, 1925 at 2 Square Robiac"
        - Signed Portrait: Sitting by Window Leaning on Left Elbow by Sylvia Beach, 1925 June 16; 1; Beach, Sylvia; 1 signed vintage print, 1 original negative, and 1 later copy print portion of 1 folder (6.75 x 5 inches) (Folder 14)
          Signed "James Joyce 16/6/1925"
        - Portrait: James Joyce Reclining in Chair by Sylvia Beach, 1925 June 16; 2; Beach, Sylvia; 1 original negative and 1 print portion of 1 folder (4.75 x 2.75 inches) (Folder 14)
          (includes original negative)
        - Portrait: James Joyce Standing With Arms Crossed by Sylvia Beach, 1925 June 16; 3; Beach, Sylvia; portion of 1 folder (4.25 x 2.5 inches) (Folder 14)
          attached note similare to inscription on reverse "James Joyce chez lui, photo par Sylvia Beach, drapeau grec derrière Joyce—le 16 juin, jour de Bloom dans Ulysses " (includes original negative)
        - Portrait: James Joyce Standing With Hands on Hips by Sylvia Beach, 1925 June 16; 1 item (7 x 5 inches) (Folder 14)
          Inscribed on reverse "Photograph by Sylvia Beach, James Joyce, Bloomsday: 16 June 1925"
        - Negatives (No Photographs): James Joyce at His Home on Bloomsday by Sylvia Beach, 1925 June 16; Beach, Sylvia; 5 original negatives (Folder 14)
      - Joyce, James: By Berenice Abbott, 1926; Abbott, Berenice, 1898-1991; more than 4 folders
        - Portrait in Profile: James Joyce With Right Hand to Forehead, 1926; 1; 2 photographs portion of 1 folder (9.25 x 7 inches) (Folder 4-5)
          Stamped on reverse "Photo Berenice Abbott, 44 rue de Bac, Paris"
        - Portrait: James Joyce With Eyes Closed and Leaning on Left Hand, 1926; 3; portion of 1 folder (9 x 7 inches (mounted in frame 17 x 14)) (Folder 6)
        - Portrait: James Joyce Wearing Eye Patch and Leaning Forward on Right Hand, 1926; 4; portion of 1 folder (9.5 x 7 inches (mounted in frame 17 x 14)) (Folder 7)
          Signed "Berenice Abbott, Paris, 1926" on recto.
        - Portrait: James Joyce Wearing Eye Patch and Leaning Back on Right Hand, 1926; 5; 2 photographs portion of 1 folder (9 x 7 inches (mounted in frame 17 x 14)) (Folder 8-9)
          One print signed "Berenice Abbott, Paris, 1926" on recto.
      - Joyce, James: Déjeuner Ulysse, 1929 June 27; 1.0 folder
        - Large Reproduction of a Group Photograph: James Joyce and Group Seated at Table, 1929 June 27; 1; portion of 1 folder (7 x 10 inches) (Folder 15)
          This is a copy print of an original once housed at La Maison des Amis des Livres. Typescript caption at bottom of print: First row (seated from left to right) Philippe Soupault, Mme James Joyce, Edouard Dujardin, Paul Valéry, Joyce, Léon Paul Fargue. Second row: (standing from left to right) Mlle Jeanne Bouquet, Mme Georges Joyce, M. Charles de la Morandière, Mlle Lucia Joyce, Mlle Lucienne Astruc, M. Philippe Fontaine, M. Thomas McGreevy, Léon Pivet, Marc Chadourne, Sylvia Beach, Adrienne Monnier, Jules Romains, Mme Paul Valéry, André Chamson, Mme Marie Scheikévitch, and Pierre de Lanux. With menu and signatures on reverse.
        - Note Explaining Origins of Photograph, undated; portion of 1 folder (Folder 15)
          "2 copies de la photo dans la bibliothèque d’Adrienne Monnier, Déjeuner Ulysse chez Léopold Vallée de Chevreuse, Saillet a fait copier cette photo et a donné 2 ex. à Sylvia, signature de Sylvia Beach effacée (?), Valéry a écrit en bas ‘Rose as a Peach’"
      - Joyce, James: With James Stephens and John Sullivan, 1929; 1.0 folder
        - Group Portrait: Stephens and Joyce Sitting on Couch With Sullivan Standing Behind, 1929; 1; New York times.; portion of 1 folder (11.75 x 8.75 inches) (Folder 16)
          signed below by all three and stamped "The New York Times, 106, rue Réaumur, Paris" (includes negative)
        - Group Portrait: Stephens, Joyce, And Sullivan Standing on the Sidewalk, 1929; 2; portion of 1 folder (7.25 x 9.5 inches, mounted on board 9 x 11.25 inches) (Folder 16)
          stamped "The New York Times, 106, rue Réaumur, Paris," inscribed on reverse "James Joyce au milieu avec à gauche le romancier irlandais James Stephens et à droit le chanteur Sullivan," stamped on reverse "Shakespeare and Company, Bookstore, 12, Rue de l’Odéon, Paris-VI e ," label on reverse of A. Bouchard, gilder and framer of paintings and engravings, 14, rue Monsieur le Prince, Paris 6 me
      - Joyce, James: By Jacques Émile Blanche, 1935; 1; 1.0 folder (5.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 17)
        Picture postcard of painted portrait by Jacques Émile Blanche, titled "James Augustine Aloysius Joyce," 1935, taken from the National Portrait Gallery, short biography on reverse with note "Printed for the National Portrait Gallery, London, by B. Matthews (Photo Printers) Ltd., Bradford, England."
      - Joyce, James: By Gisèle Freund, 1938-1939; 1; 1.0 folder (9.5 x 7.25 inches (mounted on card 11 x 9)) (Folder 10)
        Formal portrait of James Joyce standing and looking down. Initialed G. F. on recto.
      - Joyce, James: Various Portraits, 1915-1929; 1.0 folder
        - Photograph and Negative: James Joyce Playing Guitar in Trieste by Ottacaro Weiss, 1915; 1 photograph and 1 copy negative (Folder 18)
        - Portrait in Profile: James Joyce in Zurich With Beard, 1919; 1; 1 photograph portion of 1 folder (5.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 18)
        - Snapshots: James Joyce's Portrait in a German Bookshop, 1920s; 2; 5 images portion of 1 folder (2.25 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 18)
          inscribed on reverse "a Berlin bookshop in the 20s with Joyce display"
        - Snapshot: James Joyce on Beach in Holland (1927), 1; 1.0 folder (4.75 x 5 inches) (Folder 18)
          With attached note "(and alone) on the beach at Scheveningen, Holland 1927"
        - Negative (No Photograph): Portrait of James Joyce With Cap and Overcoat in Bognor, Sussex, 1923; 1 item (Folder 18)
        - Negative (No Photograph): James Joyce Standing Outside With Another Man, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
        - Negative (No Photograph): James Joyce Sitting on a Bench, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      - Joyce, James: Negatives of Joyce and Drinkwater Families in Switzerland and With the Drinkwaters, undated; 5 negatives and 1 envelope (Folder 19)
        This folder contains five negatives of the Joyce and Drinkwater family vacationing in Switzerland. Also includes a note identifying location as Lake Constance.
      - Joyce, James: Places, undated; portions of 3 boxes
        - Photographs: Dr. Borsch’s Clinic in Paris, undated; 1.0 folder
          At least one photograph by Camilla Steinbrugge.
          - Dr. Borsch’s Clinic, undated; 1; 8 images portion of 1 folder (8 x 4 inches) (Folder 3)
            Attached note "James Joyce’s room in Dr. Borsch’s clinic where the operations were performed on his eyes, corner of Rue du Regard and Rue du Cherche-Midi, Photograph by Camilla Steinbrugge"
          - The Victoria Palace Hotel, By Camilla Steinbrugge, undated; 10; 3 images portion of 1 folder (4.5 x 2.75 inches) (Folder 3)
            Written on reverse "photo C.S., Hotel Victoria Palace, rue Blaise Desgoffe"
          - Joyce’s Door in the Square Robiac, By Camilla Steinbrugge, undated; 12; portion of 1 folder (4.5 x 2.75 inches) (Folder 3)
            Written on reverse "Square Robiac (C.S.), J.J.’s door"
          - The Square Robiac by Sylvia Beach, undated; 13; portion of 1 folder (4.5 x 2.75 inches) (Folder 3)
            Written on reverse "photo SB, Sqaure Robiac"
        - Negatives: Dr. Borsch’s Clinic in Paris, undated; 1 folder (Folder 32)
        - Photographs: Various Views of Dublin, Ireland, undated; 1.0 folder
          - Storefront of Bernard Kiernan, Importer of Tea and Wine and Licensed Spirit Dealer, undated; 1; portion of 1 folder (6 x 8 inches) (Folder 4)
          - Storefront of David Byrne, Seller of Irish and Scotch Whiskies, undated; 2; portion of 1 folder (5.75 x 7.75 inches) (Folder 4)
          - View of Kingsbridge, undated; 3; portion of 1 folder (4 x 6.25 inches) (Folder 4)
          - View of Grattan Bridge From [?] Quay, Georgheyan Dublin, undated; 4; portion of 1 folder (3.25 x 5.25 inches) (Folder 4)
          - View of the River Liffey and Georgheyan Dublin, undated; 5; 2 images portion of 1 folder (3 x 5.25 inches) (Folder 4)
          - Parliament Square on the Campus of Trinity College, undated; 7; portion of 1 folder (2.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 4)
          - Bell Tower on the Campus of Trinity College, undated; 8; portion of 1 folder (2.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 4)
          - Unidentified Woman Standing on the Sidewalk, undated; 9; portion of 1 folder (2.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 4)
          - Statue of Guinness in St. Patrick’s Churchyard, undated; 10; portion of 1 folder (3.5 x 2.5 inches) (Folder 4)
          - Churchyard of St. Patrick’s Cathedral, undated; 11; portion of 1 folder (2.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 4)
          - View of a Church in Dublin, undated; 12; 5 images portion of 1 folder (3.5 x 2.5 inches) (Folder 4)
          - Photograph: Liffey Head Given to Sylvia Beach by James Joyce, undated; 7; 1.0 folder (14.5 x 11 inches) (Folder 6)
            inscribed on reverse "Given to Sylvia Beach by James Joyce"
        - Negatives: Various Views of Dublin, Ireland, undated; 1 folder (Folder 33)
        - Photographs: Doorman in Front Of "Maison Meublée, Chambres Et Appartements", undated; 2; portion of 1 folder (4.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 5)
      - Joyce, James: Sylvia Beach's Notes on Joyce Photos, undated; 1.0 folder
        - Notes on Envelope and Paper Concerning SB’s Photos of James Joyce From Paris, Toulon, And Brussels, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Katz, Leslie, undated; 1; 1.0 folder (4.75 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 21)
      Snapshot of Leslie Katz walking on the sidewalk. Inscribed on reverse "to Sylvia with love and admiration, Leslie"
    - Larbaud, Valéry, 1920-1922; 1.0 folder
      - Envelope With Notes, undated; portion of 1 folder (Folder 22)
        "Larbaud with hippopotamus at zoo in Lisbon, copied May 31st 1961. M. Bernard Delvaille asked me to give him a copy, on reflection thought I should keep for Mercure publication Shakespeare and Company "
      - Snapshot: View of Hippopotamus at a Zoo in Lisbon, undated; 1; portion of 1 folder (2.75 x 2 inches, mounted on card 5.5 x 4.5 inches) (Folder 22)
        Captioned "Abra mais!," inscribed "Miss Sylvia Beach from her friends the Hippopotamus and Valery Larbaud"
      - Snapshot: Valéry Larbaud Feeding a Hippopotamus at a Zoo in Lisbon, undated; 2; 2 copies (6.25 x 4.25 inches) (Folder 22)
      - Copy Negative: Valéry Larbaud Feeding a Hippopotamus at a Zoo in Lisbon, undated; 1 item (Folder 22)
      - Photograph of Painted portrait: Valéry Larbaud by Paul-Émile Bécat, 1922; 1; portion of 1 folder (8 x 6.5 inches) (Folder 22)
        Stamped on reverse "Vizzavona, 65 Rue du Bac—Paris 7e"
      - Photograph of Drawn portrait: Valéry Larbaud by Paul-Émile Bécat, 1920; 2; portion of 1 folder (10.5 x 8.25 inches) (Folder 22)
      - Photograph of Drawn portrait: Valéry Larbaud From the Bibliothèque Municipale De Vichy, undated; 3; portion of 1 folder (10.75 x 8.75 inches) (Folder 22)
        Inscribed on reverse "L’original se trouve à la Bibliothèque municipale de Vichy (allies) en France, Fonds Valery Larbaud," stamped on reverse "Shakespeare and Company, Bookshop, 12, Rue de l’Odéon, Paris VIe"
      - Portrait: Valéry Larbaud in Alicante, undated; 1; 1 mounted vintage print and 1 copy print portion of 1 folder (5.5 x 3.5 inches (mounted on board 9 x 7)) (Folder 22)
        Inscribed "To Sylvia Beach from a friend and admirer, Valéry Larbaud." Blind stamp of photographer is illegible in photograph; photograph itself appears to be a vintage copy print.
    - Lawrence, D.H., 1932 June; 1.0 folder
      - Signed Photograph of drawing: D.H. Lawrence by Millicent Beveridge, undated; 1; portion of 1 folder (8.75 x 6.75 inches) (Folder 23)
        Signed on front and reverse "D.H. Lawrence," stamped on reverse "Shakespeare and Company, Bookshop, 12, Rue de l’Odéon, Paris VIe"
      - Photographic Postcard: D.H. Lawrence’s Grave in Vence, 1932 June; 2; portion of 1 folder (5.25 x 3.25 inches) (Folder 23)
        Sent by Mlle Patard, note on reverse "Cimetière de Vence, Tombe de D.H. Lawrence, Juin 1932"
      - Snapshots: D.H. Lawrence’s Grave in Vence, undated; 3; 2 images portion of 1 folder (2.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 23)
        One image captioned "Budgen’s photo of D.H. Lawrence’s grave at Vence (removed to Taos)," inscribed on reverse "close-up of Lawrence’s grave, wall at end." Other: captioned "Budgen’s photo showing terrace with D.H. Lawrence’s grave at Vence," inscribed on reverse "view of the terrace where Lawrence is buried, his grave marked X"
      - Mounted Portrait: D.H. Lawrence by Nickolas Muray, undated; 5; Muray, Nickolas, 1892-1965; portion of 1 folder (10.25 x 8 inches) (Folder 23)
    - Lawrence, T.E., undated; 1; 1.0 folder (9 x 6.5 inches) (Folder 24)
      Print of a bust (sculpture) of Lawrence.
    - Lewis, Sinclair, undated; 1.0 folder
      - Copy Print: Portrait of Lewis Sinclair by Adeda, undated; 1; portion of 1 folder (9.5 x 7.25 inches) (Folder 25)
      - Copy Print: Portrait of Lewis Sinclair in Hat and Overcoat by Man Ray, undated; 2; Man Ray, 1890-1976; portion of 1 folder (9.5 x 7.25 inches, mounted on card 11 x 8.75 inches) (Folder 25)
      - Copy Print: Lewis Sinclair in Florence, undated; 3; 2 copies (9.5 x 7.25 inches) (Folder 25)
        Written on reverse "Sinclair Lewis dans sa villa à Florence"
    - Lewis, Wyndham, undated; 1; 1.0 folder (9 x 6.75 inches) (Folder 26)
      Print (non-photographic) of a formal portrait, signed "Wyndham Lewis"
    - Linossier, Raymonde, 1921; 1 folder
      Includes an image of Raymonde Linossier as a child.
      - Portrait: Raymonde Linossier as a Child, undated; 1 item (Folder 27)
      - Portraits: Raymonde Linossier in Shakespeare and Company by Sylvia Beach, 1921; Beach, Sylvia; 1 item (Folder 27)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1927; 1; portion of 1 folder (11 x 8.5 inches) (Folder 28)
      Photograph of drawn portrait by Paul-Émile Bécat. Inscribed "For Sylvia, affectionately, Archibald MacLeish." Includes a copy print of the same image, with the inscription.
    - Mansfield, Katherine, undated; 1 folder
      - Clipping of a Formal portrait: Katherine Mansfield, undated; 1; portion of 1 folder (4.5 x 3.25 inches) (Folder 29)
      - Signed Clipping of a Formal portrait: Katherine Mansfield, undated; 2; portion of 1 folder (7.5 x 5 inches) (Folder 29)
    - Mathews, Jackson, 1934-1960; 1.0 folder
      - Formal portrait: Jackson Mathews, 1934; 1; 1 vintage print and 2 copy prints portion of 1 folder (6 x 3.5 inches, mounted on card 10 x 8.75 inches) (Folder 30)
        Written on reverse: "Jackson Mathews as actor—Eugene, Oregon 1934"
      - Snapshot: Jackson Mathews Sitting With a Woman, undated; 2; portion of 1 folder (4 x 5.75 inches) (Folder 30)
      - Snapshot: Jackson Mathews Standing Outside With a Woman, 1955; 3; portion of 1 folder (4.5 x 3.25 inches) (Folder 30)
      - Snapshot: Jackson Mathews Outside With His Dog, Pomme, 1958 August; 4; portion of 1 folder (3.25 x 4.5 inches) (Folder 30)
      - Snapshot: Jackson Mathews' Dog Pomme, 1960; 5; 3 images portion of 1 folder (3.5 x 2.5 inches) (Folder 30)
        Inscribed on reverse "Pomme, March 1960"
    - Maurois, André, 1924; 1; 1.0 folder (11 x 8.75 inches) (Folder 31)
      Photograph of drawn portrait signed by Aaron Bilis 1924. Inscribed "À Sylvia Beach parce qu’elle aime les livres avec la même passion que moi—André Maurois"
    - McAlmon, Robert, 1920-1923 July 20; portions of 3 boxes
      - McAlmon, Robert: By Man Ray, 1923 July 20; portions of 2 boxes
        - Inscribed Formal Portrait: Robert McAlmon Seated by Man Ray, undated; 4; Man Ray, 1890-1976; portion of 1 folder (9.5 x 7 inches (mounted in frame 14.5 x 11.5)) (Folder 4)
          Inscribed "To Sylvia Beach from Bob McAlmon," signed "M R Paris"
        - Formal Portrait: Robert McAlmon in Shirt and Tie by Man Ray, undated; 5; Man Ray, 1890-1976; portion of 1 folder (5.5 x 3.5 inches (mounted in frame 14.5 x 11.5)) (Folder 5)
        - Signed Portrait: Robert McAlmon by Man Ray, undated; 5.1; Man Ray, 1890-1976; portion of 1 folder (5.5 x 3.5 inches (mounted in frame 14.5 x 11.5)) (Folder 5)
        - Signed Formal Portrait: Robert McAlmon in Shirt and Tie by Man Ray, 1923 July 20; Man Ray, 1890-1976; 1 folder (7.75 x 5.75 inches, mounted on card 11.75 x 9.25 inches) (Folder 6)
        - Formal Portrait: Robert McAlmon With Mustache by Man Ray, undated; 6; Man Ray, 1890-1976; portion of 1 folder (5.5 x 3.5 inches (mounted in frame 14.5 x 11.5)) (Folder 7)
      - McAlmon, Robert: In Shakespeare and Company by Sylvia Beach, 1920; 1 folder
        - Snapshot: Robert McAlmon Standing in Profile With Hands in Pockets by Sylvia Beach, circa 1920; 1; Beach, Sylvia; 2 vintage prints, 1 later print, and 1 original negative portion of 1 folder (4.25 x 2.75 inches) (Folder 32)
          Inscribed on reverse "McAlmon at Shakespeare and Company, by Sylvia"
        - Snapshot: Robert McAlmon Standing in Profile With One Hand in Pocket by Sylvia Beach, circa 1920; 2; Beach, Sylvia; 1 vintage print, 1 later print, and 1 original negative (4.5 x 2.75 inches) (Folder 32)
          (includes original negative) (See also photograph 6 in Box 258, Folder 14.)
        - Snapshot: Robert McAlmon Standing and Facing the Camera by Sylvia Beach, circa 1920; 3; Beach, Sylvia; 1 vintage print, 2 later prints, and 1 original negative (4.25 x 2.75 inches) (Folder 32)
        - Snapshot: Robert McAlmon Standing and Facing the Camera Looking Up by Sylvia Beach, circa 1920; 4; Beach, Sylvia; 1 vintage print, 1 copy print, and 1 original negative portion of 1 folder (4.25 x 2.75 inches) (Folder 32)
          (See also photographs 2, 3, and 4 in Box 258, Folder 13.)
      - Signed portrait: Robert McAlmon, undated; 1; 2 signed copies (4.75 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 1)
        Signed "Bob McAlmon"
      - Photographic postcard: Robert McAlmon Seated at a Desk With Typewriter, undated; 2; portion of 1 folder (5.5 x 3.5 inches) (Folder 1)
      - Formal portrait: Robert McAlmon by Henri Martinie, undated; 3; Martinie, A.-H. (A.-Henri), b. 1881; portion of 1 folder (8.5 x 5.5 inches) (Folder 1)
        Image is very faded. Signed by Henri Martinie.
      - Formal Portrait: Robert McAlmon in Profile, undated; 4; portion of 1 folder (8.75 x 5.5 inches, mounted on card 10 x 6.5 inches) (Folder 1)
        Print is very faded. Possibly by Henri Martinie.
      - Formal Portrait: Robert McAlmon in Profile, undated; 5; portion of 1 folder (8.5 x 6.25 inches) (Folder 1)
      - Snapshot: Robert McAlmon in Ronda Countryside, circa 1920; 6; portion of 1 folder (2.75 x 1.75 inches) (Folder 1)
        Written on reverse "Ronda, Bob McAlmon 1920 (?)"
      - Snapshot: Robert McAlmon Holding a Snake in Mexico, undated; 7; portion of 1 folder (3.5 x 5.5 inches) (Folder 1)
        Captioned "Bob McAlmon in Mexico"